Guide to the Campus Ministry Records 1954-1995
Pacific Lutheran University, Archives and Special Collections
Campus Ministry Records
1954-1995
Pacific Lutheran University Archives and Special Collections 12180 Park Avenue S. Tacoma, WA 98447 253-531-6900 http://www.plu.edu/archives
OPVARCH1_20
Campus Ministry
10 boxes (15 lin.ft), 1 scrapbook, 85 photographs
Records documenting the founding, organization, management and running of Campus Ministry from the years 1955 to 1995.
Historical note:
The Student Congregation of Pacific Lutheran College (PLC) was formed in 1955 through the combined efforts of President Eastvold, the PLC faculty and the student body. It was created with the intent to be a congregation made up of and run by the students of PLC, functioning under the Evangelical Lutheran Church (ELC). It functioned the same as any ELC congregation of the time, with a Church Council and its officers, a Board of Trustees to handle material matters, and a Board of Deacons of handle spiritual matters. The recently constructed Chapel-Music-Speech Building was to function as its place of worship, and the first pastor called to minister to the Student Congregation was Reverend Robert W. Lutnes.
Pastor Lutnes served as Pastor to the Student Congregation during its formative years, at first only overseeing the congregation and its needs, but by his final year (1958) acting as official advisor to all of the religious clubs on campus. Also in 1958, he was officially asked to assist the Dean of students in arranging speakers for the required Chapel services that took place four days a week in the Chapel-Music-Speech Building--a task that had previously been the responsibility of the Dean and the President.
Reverend John Larsgaard was called to be the second pastor to the Student Congregation in 1959. In 1960, Pacific Lutheran College became Pacific Lutheran University (PLU), and in 1962 President Eastvold resigned, to be replaced by Dr. Mortvedt. With the steady growth of the Student Congregation, the workload quickly became too heavy for one pastor to handle everything. Thus, a number of different Associate Pastors--many of them housefathers--were hired part-time to help ease the burden. They included Pastor "Pops" Malmin (housefather of Old Main (Harstad)), Pastor S.M. Moe (housefather in Ivy Hall), Pastor Alf Kraabel (housefather in Pflueger), and Joseph Shefveland (Foss Hall). By 1966 the work load became heavy enough that a second full-time pastor became necessary and Reverend Morris Dalton was called to be Associate Pastor to the Student Congregation.
In addition to his duties as Pastor to the University Congregation, Pastor Larsgaard was also University Chaplain, and therefore in charge of organizing Chapel. Ever since the Chapel-Music-Speech Building was built in 1952, all students had been required to attend Chapel four days a week. In 1966, though, the student body began to argue against mandatory Chapel attendance. Pastor Larsgaard agreed with the students, supporting voluntary Chapel for everyone, and the school year of 1967-1968 was the first year that students were not required to attend Chapel.
Both Pastor Larsgaard and President Mortvedt left PLU in 1969. President Mortvedt was replaced by Dr. Wiegman, and Pastor Larsgaard by Reverend Don Taylor. This was a time of upheaval and change at PLU. It was generally considered that the Student Congregation was not meeting the needs of the students on campus, and President Weigman felt that it was important to find alternate worship possibilities and a different form of organization for religious groups on campus. In response to this, the Religious Life Council was formed as a governing body for all religious groups on campus. Additionally, the Religious Life Council was given the authority to appoint ministers to the university. Thus, the ministers called to the University were no longer Pastors to the Student Congregation, but Ministers to the University at large, with the Student Congregation being only one of their responsibilities.
Following this change in structure, Pastor Dalton's contract was not renewed, and Pastor Taylor's was only renewed for one year. In 1971, Reverend Gordon Lathrop was called to be University Minister. He worked as the only pastor on campus for two years, though he had interns to help him with his duties. In 1973, the Student Congregation revised its constitution and changed its name to the University Congregation. In that same year, the workload again became too heavy for one pastor, even with the help of interns, and Reverend James Beckman was called to minister alongside Pastor Lathrop. During their two years together, the PLU administration reached a point of upheaval. President Wiegman took a leave of absence for his final year as University President, and Provost Jungkuntz took over for him. In 1975, Dr. William Rieke was chosen as PLU's next president.
Pastor Lathrop left PLU in 1975, and Reverend Donald Jerke was called to take his place. Pastor Jerke worked alongside Pastor Beckman until 1976, when Pastor Beckman died of cancer. That year Reverend Ronald Tellefson was called to be Campus Minister alongside Pastor Jerke. In 1978, the Religious Life Council revised its constitution and changed its name to the Campus Ministry Council. One year later, Pastor Jerke resigned his post as University Minister and accepted a position as Vice President for Student Life.
Pastor Tellefson stayed as University Minister for ten years. During that time the Beckman Memorial Lectureship Series was initiated in Memory of Pastor Beckman, the first being held in 1978. In 1980, Reverend Ron Pierre Vignec was called to be Associate Pastor. Together he and Tellefson saw the establishment of ties between PLU and Africa, the creation of the Chicago Folk Services, the 1982 Peacemaking Conference, and another revision of the Campus Ministry Council's constitution. Pastor Vignec left PLU in 1985, the same year that the University Congregation celebrated its 30th Anniversary. Pastor Tellefson stayed as Campus Minister until 1987, when he accepted the appointment as Director of Church and University Support at PLU.
In 1987, three University Ministers were called simultaneously to serve PLU. Reverends Daniel Erlander, Susan Briehl and Martin Wells ministered to PLU until 1994.
Records documenting the history of Campus ministry at Pacific Lutheran University. Collection includes sermons, backgrounds of pastors, chapel papers and bulletins, religious life council records, student congregation records and university congregation records including papers and bulletins.
Series I. Campus Pastors
Subseries A. The Lutnes Years, 1955-1958
Subseries B. The Larsgaard Years, 1959-1969
Subseries C. The Taylor Years, 1969-1971
Subseries D. The Beckman/Lathrop/Jerke Years, 1971-1978
Subseries E. The Tellefson/Vignec/Rieke Years, 1978-1987
Subseries F. The Erlander/Wells/Briehl Years, 1987-1994
Subseries H. Job Descriptions/Internships
Subseries I. Publicity
Series II. Chapel
Subseries A. Chapel Papers
Subseries B. Chapel Bulletins
Series III. Religious Life Council/Campus Ministry Council, 1970-1994
Series IV. Student Congregation/University Congregation, 1955-1994
Subseries A. Student Congregation Records
Subseries B. Student Congregation Bulletins
The local histories are available for research
Transferred to archives by Campus Ministry
To search and view digitized images relating to this and other collections, visit our Digital Assets Website
This collection is indexed under the following headings in the online catalog. Researchers desiring materials about related topics, persons, or places should search the catalog using these headings.
Lutnes, Robert W.; Larsgaard, John; Kraabel, Alf M.; Dalton, Morris; Taylor, Donald; Lathrop, Gordon; Beckman, James; Jerke, Donald; Tellefson, Ronald; Vignec, Ron Pierre; Rieke, Stephen
Campus Ministry; Student Congregation; Evangelical Lutheran Church; Chapel-Music-Speech Building; Religious Life Council; Campus Ministry Council; University Congregation; Bread for the World (Organization)
Chapel; Sermons; Peace
Africa; Namibia
Religion
University and college chaplains; University minister; Campus Minister
The following section contains a detailed listing of the materials in the collection.
- Campus Pastors, 1
  - The Lutnes Years, 1955-1958; A
    Pastor Robert W. Lutnes was Pastor for the Student Congregation at Pacific Lutheran College (PLC) from the time that it was established in 1955 until 1958. Prior to being pastor at PLC, he taught English there for two years. He is the author of Ever One God (Augsburg Publishing House, 1955). In 1954 he wrote a pageant called "The Eternal Slave" for PLC's Sixtieth Anniversary Celebration. Events that took place during his time as pastor were Mission Emphasis Week, Spiritual Emphasis Week, Family Life Conference, and the founding of the Student Congregation.
    - Mission Emphasis Week, 1954 (Box-folder 1.1)
    - Eternal Slave, 1954 (Box-folder 1.2)
    - Pilgrim, date unknown (Box-folder 1.3)
    - Spiritual Emphasis Week, 1955-1958 (Box-folder 1.4)
    - Seedtime, 1958 (Box-folder 1.5)
    - Correspondence, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 1.6)
  - The Larsgaard Years, 1959-1969; B
    Pastor Larsgaard was Pastor of Student Congregation and University Chaplain at Pacific Lutheran University (PLU) from 1959 to 1969. During Larsgaard's time, PLU hosted Spiritual Emphasis Week, Mission Emphasis Week, and Faith in Life Week, as well as the Family Life Conference. In 1967, chapel attendance was changed from mandatory to voluntary. Associate Pastors during Larsgaard's time were Malmin (1960-1962), Moe (1961-1967), Kraabel (1962-1967), Shefveland (1965-1967) and Dalton (1967-1969).
    - Spiritual Emphasis Week, 1959-1962 (Box-folder 1.7)
    - Larsgaard Correspondence, 1958-1959 (Box-folder 1.8)
    - Larsgaard Correspondence, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 1.9)
    - Larsgaard Correspondence, 1960-1961 (Box-folder 1.10)
    - Larsgaard Correspondence, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 1.11)
    - Larsgaard Correspondence, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 1.12)
    - Larsgaard Correspondence, 1964-1965 (Box-folder 1.13)
    - Larsgaard Correspondence, 1965-1966 (Box-folder 1.14)
    - Larsgaard Correspondence, 1966-1967 (Box-folder 1.15)
    - Larsgaard Correspondence, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 1.16)
    - Larsgaard Correspondence, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 1.17)
    - Pastor's Inquirers' Class, n.d. (Box-folder 2.1)
    - Family Life Conference, 1959 (Box-folder 2.2)
    - LSA, 1960-1961 (Box-folder 2.3)
    - Reformation Festival, 1960-1961 (Box-folder 2.4)
    - Faith in Life Week, 1963-1966 (Box-folder 2.5)
    - League Interest Fellowship Team, 1965-1967 (Box-folder 2.6)
    - Listening Witness, 1965-1968 (Box-folder 2.7)
    - Lutheran World Federation, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 2.8)
    - CALL committee, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 2.9)
    - Chapel Attendance, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 2.10)
  - The Taylor/Dalton Years, 1969-1971; C
    Donald W. Taylor was Pastor for the Student Congregation and University Chaplain for Pacific Lutheran University (PLU) from 1969 to 1971. During his time at PLU, the Religious Life committee was formed to address the religious needs of the students (1971). Though the Student Congregation continued to be the dominant worship community at PLU, other religious groups gained popularity and attendance. Efforts were made to give students the opportunity to worship with off-campus congregations. Student Congregation services were moved to the Chris Knudsen Hall in the University Center. Morris Dalton was his Associate Pastor from 1969-1970.
    - Dalton Correspondence, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 2.11)
    - Taylor Correspondence, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 2.12)
    - Taylor Correspondence, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 2.13)
  - The Lathrop/Beckman /Jerke Years, 1971-1978; D
    Gordon Lathrop was University Minister for Pacific Lutheran University (PLU) from 1971 to 1975. James Beckman served as University Minister at Pacific Lutheran University (PLU) from 1973 until his death in 1976. He spent one year as an intern at PLU before he was called to be University Minister. Don Jerke served as University Minister of Pacific Lutheran University from 1975 to 1978. He became vice president of student life in 1978 and retained the position until his death in 1981. Events during Lathrop's time as Pastor at PLU include the Staley Distinguished Christian Lectureship Series, "The Church and Social Change" symposium, "The Celebration of the Gospel with Herb Brokering," the first All Campus Fast, Student Congregation's name change to University Congregation, and the renovation of Tower Chapel. In 1973, the need for two full time pastors was expressed and Beckman was hired as a second University Minister. Bread for the World was founded, PLU was host to Madelyn Murray O'Hare in 1974 and Dr. Helmut Thielicke in 1975. Pastor Jerke took over for Pastor Lathrop in 1975. Notable events to happen during Jerke's time include the tragic death of Pastor James Beckman and the installation of Pastor Ron Tellefson; the revision of the Religious Life Council's constitution in which the council's name was changed to Campus Ministry Council, additions made to Tower Chapel, and the Faith in Life forum.
    - Lathrop Correspondence, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 2.14)
    - Lathrop Correspondence, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 2.15)
    - Lathrop Correspondence, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 2.16)
    - Lathrop Correspondence, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 2.17)
    - Lutheran Youth Alive, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 2.18)
    - Staley Distinguished Scholar Lectureship, 1972-1976 (Box-folder 3.1)
    - Lutheran Student Movement, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 3.2)
    - Beckman correspondence, 1973-1976 (Box-folder 3.3)
    - Beckman Sermons, 1970-1973 (Box-folder 3.4)
    - Beckman Sermons, 1974 (Box-folder 3.5)
    - Beckman Sermons, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 3.6)
    - The Beckman Files, Index (Box-folder 3.7)
    - The Beckman Files, B (Box-folder 3.8)
    - The Beckman Files, C (Box-folder 3.9)
    - The Beckman Files, D (Box-folder 3.10)
    - The Beckman Files, E (Box-folder 3.11)
    - The Beckman Files, F (Box-folder 3.12)
    - The Beckman Files, G (Box-folder 3.13)
    - The Beckman Files, H (Box-folder 3.14)
    - The Beckman Files, I (Box-folder 3.15)
    - The Beckman Files, J (Box-folder 4.1)
    - The Beckman Files, L (Box-folder 4.2)
    - The Beckman Files, M (Box-folder 4.3)
    - The Beckman Files, N (Box-folder 4.4)
    - The Beckman Files, O (Box-folder 4.5)
    - The Beckman Files, P (Box-folder 4.6)
    - The Beckman Files, Q R (Box-folder 4.7)
    - The Beckman Files, S (Box-folder 4.8)
    - The Beckman Files, T (Box-folder 4.9)
    - The Beckman Files, U V (Box-folder 4.10)
    - The Beckman Files, W X Y Z (Box-folder 4.11)
    - The Beckman Files, Worship and Liturgy (Box-folder 4.12)
    - The Beckman Files, Christmas (Box-folder 4.13)
    - The Beckman Files, Lent (Box-folder 4.14)
    - The Beckman Files, Easter (Box-folder 4.15)
    - The Beckman Files, Offertory (Box-folder 4.16)
    - The Beckman Files, Sermons (Box-folder 4.17)
    - The Beckman Files, Day of Pentecost (Box-folder 5.1)
    - The Beckman Files, Santa Lucia (Box-folder 5.2)
    - The Beckman Files, Third Sunday in Advent (Box-folder 5.3)
    - The Beckman Files, Christmas Day (Box-folder 5.4)
    - The Beckman Files, First Sunday after Christmas (Box-folder 5.5)
    - The Beckman Files, Second Sunday after Christmas (Box-folder 5.6)
    - The Beckman Files, Topical Outlines (Box-folder 5.7)
    - The Beckman Files, Saints Days/Feast Days (Box-folder 5.8)
    - The Beckman Files, Pentecost (Box-folder 5.9)
    - The Beckman Files, Church Year (Box-folder 5.10)
    - The Beckman Files, Epiphany (Box-folder 5.11)
    - The Beckman Files, Luke (Box-folder 5.12)
    - The Beckman Files, Matthew (Box-folder 5.13)
    - The Beckman Files, Mark (Box-folder 5.14)
    - The Beckman Files, John (Box-folder 5.15)
    - The Beckman Files, Acts (Box-folder 5.16)
    - The Beckman Files, Romans (Box-folder 5.17)
    - The Beckman Files, I Corinthians (Box-folder 5.18)
    - The Beckman Files, II Corinthians (Box-folder 5.19)
    - The Beckman Files, Galatians (Box-folder 5.20)
    - The Beckman Files, Ephesians (Box-folder 5.21)
    - The Beckman Files, Philippians (Box-folder 5.22)
    - The Beckman Files, Philemon (Box-folder 5.23)
    - The Beckman Files, Hebrews (Box-folder 5.24)
    - The Beckman Files, James (Box-folder 5.25)
    - The Beckman Files, Revelations (Box-folder 5.26)
    - The Beckman Files, The Disciples (Box-folder 5.27)
    - The Beckman Files, "James Beckman" (Box-folder 5.28)
    - The Beckman Files, Synoptic Parallels (Box-folder 5.29)
    - The Beckman Worship Handbook (Box-folder 5.30)
    - Beckman Death and Memorial, 1976 (Box-folder 6.1)
    - Jerke Correspondence, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 6.2)
    - Jerke Sermons, 1976-1978 (Box-folder 6.3)
    - Jerke Notes and Correspondence, 1976-1978 (Box-folder 6.4)
    - Jerke Publication, 1984 (Box-folder 6.5)
  - The Tellefson/Vignec/Rieke Years, 1977-1987; E
    Ronald Tellefson was University Pastor at Pacific Lutheran University from 1977 until 1987. Significant events during his time include the Faith in Life Forum, Beckman Memorial Lectureship, the creation of Chicago Folk Services, the Peacemaking Conference, the PLU for Africa Week, the establishment of ties with Namibia, and the University Congregation's 30th Anniversary Celebration. After leaving his post as University Pastor, Tellefson was appointed Director of Church and University Support at PLU. Associate Pastors to Tellefson were Ron Pierre Vignec (1980-1985) and Stephen Rieke (1985-1986).
    - Beckman Memorial Lectureship, 1978-1984 (Box-folder 6.1)
    - Religious Emphasis Student Questionnaire, 1977 (Box-folder 6.2)
    - Religious Emphasis Student Questionnaire, 1979 (Box-folder 6.3)
    - Religious Emphasis Student Questionnaire, 1979 (Box-folder 7.1)
    - Religious Emphasis Student Questionnaire, 1980 (Box-folder 7.2)
    - Religious Emphasis Student Survey, n.d. (Box-folder 7.3)
    - Banners and Vestments, 1975-1979 (Box-folder 7.4)
    - Sermons, n.d. (Box-folder 7.5)
    - Ronald Tellefson, 1976-1985 (Box-folder 7.6)
    - Vicar Larson, 1978-1979 (Box-folder 7.7)
    - Vicar Briehl, 1979 (Box-folder 7.8)
    - Vignec Call, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 7.9)
    - Peace Literature/Nuclear Papers, 1981 (Box-folder 7.10)
    - World Hunger Week, 1981-1983 (Box-folder 7.11)
    - Ron Pierre Vignec, 1984 (Box-folder 7.12)
    - News Clippings, 1981-1984 (Box-folder 7.13)
    - Thirtieth Anniversary, 1985 (Box-folder 7.14)
    - Rieke, Stephen, 1985 (Box-folder 7.15)
  - The Erlander/Wells/Briehl Years, 1987-1994; F
    Daniel Erlander, Martin Wells, and Susan Briehl were University Pastors at Pacific Lutheran University (PLU) from 1986 to 1994.
    - Briehl/Erlander/Wells, 1986-1994 (Box-folder 7.16)
    - Erlander--Agnes and Donna (Box-folder 7.17)
    - Erlander Publications, 1981 (Box-folder 7.18)
- Chapel, Series II
  - Chapel Papers, A
    Includes bulletins for Convocations, Chapel Schedules, papers pertaining directly to Chapel at Pacific Lutheran University, and advertisements for chapel from 1966 to 2005.
    - Convocations, 1950-1976 (Box-folder 8.1)
    - Chapel Schedules, 1966-1975 (Box-folder 8.2)
    - Chapel Papers, 1962-1992 (Box-folder 8.3)
    - Chapel Advertisements and Announcements, 1966-1995 (Box-folder 8.4)
    - Chapel Advertisements and Announcements, 1996-2005 (Box-folder 8.5)
  - Chapel Bulletins, B
    - Chapel Bulletins, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 8.6)
    - Chapel Bulletins, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 8.7)
    - Chapel Bulletins, 1964-1965 (Box-folder 8.8)
    - Chapel Bulletins, 1965-1966 (Box-folder 9.1)
    - Chapel Bulletins, 1966-1967 (Box-folder 9.2)
    - Chapel Bulletins, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 9.3)
    - Chapel Bulletins, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 9.4)
    - Chapel Bulletins, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 9.5)
    - Chapel Bulletins, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 9.6)
    - Chapel Bulletins, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 9.7)
    - Chapel Bulletins, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 9.8)
    - Chapel Bulletins, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 9.9)
    - Chapel Bulletins, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 10.1)
    - Chapel Bulletins, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 10.2)
    - Chapel Bulletins, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 10.3)
    - Chapel Bulletins, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 10.4)
    - Chapel Bulletins, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 10.5)
    - Chapel Bulletins, 1976-1977 (Box-folder 10.6)
    - Chapel Bulletins, 1976-1977 (Box-folder 10.7)
    - Chapel Bulletins, 1977-1978 (Box-folder 10.8)
    - Chapel Bulletins, 1977-1978 (Box-folder 10.9)
    - Chapel Bulletins, 1978-1979 (Box-folder 10.10)
    - Chapel Bulletins, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 10.11)
    - Chapel Bulletins, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 10.12)
    - Chapel Bulletins, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 10.13)
    - Chapel Bulletins, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 10.14)
    - Chapel Bulletins, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 10.15)
- Religious Life Council/Campus Ministry Council, 1969-1994; Series III
  Includes minutes from Religious Life Council meetings, includes Religious life Council Constitution and Religious Clubs.
  - Religious Life Council, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 11.1)
  - Religious Life Council, 1970-1071 (Box-folder 11.2)
  - Religious Life Council, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 11.3)
  - Religious Life Council, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 11.4)
  - Religious Life Council, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 11.5)
  - Religious Life Council, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 11.6)
  - Religious Life Council, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 11.7)
  - Religious Life Council, 1976-1977 (Box-folder 11.8)
  - Religious Life Council, 1977-1978 (Box-folder 11.9)
  - Religious Life Council, 1978-1979 (Box-folder 11.10)
  - Religious Life Council, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 11.11)
  - Religious Life Council, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 11.12)
  - Religious Life Council, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 11.13)
  - Religious Life Council, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 11.14)
  - Religious Life Council, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 11.15)
  - Religious Life Council, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 11.16)
  - Religious Life Council, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 11.17)
  - Religious Life Council, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 11.18)
  - Religious Life Council, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 11.19)
  - Religious Life Council, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 11.20)
  - Religious Life Council, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 11.21)
  - Religious Life Council, 1990-1991 (Box-folder 11.22)
  - Religious Life Council, 1991-1992 (Box-folder 11.23)
  - Religious Life Council, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 11.24)
  - Religious Life Council Constitutions (Box-folder 11.25)
  - Religious Life Council Clubs (Box-folder 11.26)
- Student Congregation/University Congregation, 1955-1994; Series IV
  - Student Congregation Papers, 1955-1994; A
    Includes minutes of Student Congregation meetings, minutes of Board of Trustees for the Student Congregation, minutes of the Board of Deacons, Constitutions of the Student Congregation, limited correspondence directly related to Student Congregation, Budgets., Treasurers' log books, ballots and congratulatory letters for the election of officers.
    - Student Congregation, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 12.1)
    - Student Congregation, 1956-1957 (Box-folder 12.2)
    - Student Congregation, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 12.3)
    - Treasurer's Book, 1955-1958 (Box-folder 12.4)
    - Student Congregation, 1958-1959 (Box-folder 12.5)
    - Student Congregation, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 12.6)
    - Student Congregation, 1960-1961 (Box-folder 12.7)
    - Student Congregation, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 12.8)
    - Student Congregation, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 12.9)
    - Student Congregation, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 12.10)
    - Student Congregation, 1964-1965 (Box-folder 12.11)
    - Student Congregation, 1965-1966 (Box-folder 12.12)
    - Treasurer's Log, 1965-1966 (Box-folder 12.13)
    - Treasurer's Book, 1964-1966 (Box-folder 12.14)
    - Student Congregation, 1966-1967 (Box-folder 12.15)